



Prague, Czech Republic



lukas.bunat@gmail.com



+420 731 277 533



www.lukasbunat.net



linkedin.com/in/lukasbunat/



Languages

- Czech, Slovak (native)
- English (Full professional proficiency)



Certificates

- CISCO Academy CCNA 1
- AutoDesk AutoCAD, Inventor
- UNESCO CCAP, South Korea



Skills

- C++, Java, SQL, PHP, Bash, HTML
- MS Office, TeXStudio, AutoCAD
- Innovative analytical problem solving
- Leadership with good decision making
- Projects' cycle management skills
- Cross-culture communication skills
- Adaptability, Team player



Interests

- New innovative technologies
- Travelling, cross-culture encounters
- Reading & self-developing
- Sports volleyball, fitness

Lukas Bunat

Software Developer, Data architect

I am a 23-year-old, tech of any kind enthusiast. I have had gradually studied at four different universities in Europe and Asia. I take pride of my international working experiences in software development, managing big data and networking. Additionally, I have also worked in customer service (financial) and education sector. My passion is traveling, especially cross-culture encounters.

My technically analytical thinking allows me finding clever solutions. Furthermore, my vast knowledge, many different skills and abilities, as well as strong opinions, guarantee good decision making. I steadfastly hard-working towards my dreams and goals. I can easily learn new things, cooperate and communicate with others, no matter their background. I am the one, who always wants to lead others by using my own creativity. Yet still reflecting suggestions from others.



Experiences

Big Data Architect Trainee | 10/2017 - 12/2017

Comillas Pontifical University, Madrid, Spain Application of Clustering Methods for Discovering Patterns of Energy

Network Engineer Trainee | 03/2017 - 06/2017

Kyungpook National University, Daegu, South Korea Network Simulations on Cooja Simulator

Paper-Form Blueprints Convert | 09/2014 – 03/2015

Self-employed, Individual Projects

Converting paper form of blueprints into digital form using AutoCAD

I am working as a tutor for international students in international student club at Czech Technical University since 2014. I have worked as a financial advisor in OVB in 2011-2013 and as a teacher at Korean high schools.



Education

Czech Technical University, Prague, Czech Republic Information Systems and Management, 2014 – Present

Kyungpook National University, Daegu, South Korea Exchange studies, 2017

Indian Institute of Technology Madras, Chennai, India Exchange studies, 2016

Delft University of Technology, Delft, Netherlands The ATHENS Programme, Case study of Earthquakes in Netherland, 2016

Mayflower College of English, Plymouth, United Kingdom Summer language school, 2012